<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Betaflight mini Site</title>
    <link>https://betaflight.fr/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Betaflight mini Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 21:49:20 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://betaflight.fr/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Betaflight 3.3 Advanced filters</title>
      <link>https://betaflight.fr/blog/2018/02/16/bf3-3_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://betaflight.fr/blog/2018/02/16/bf3-3_4/</guid>
      <description>Betaflight 3.3 Release will be ready for March 1st. New feature : Advanced filters New advanced filters have been added to Betaflight 3.3.
Advanced filters are not working with all flight controllers and must be activate with caution.
Fast Kalman has been replaced by Biquad RC+FIR2. It s now more easy to activate and use.
You just need to specify cutoff Hz parameter directly. Flightcontroller with F4 processor is advised.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Betaflight 3.3 Anti-Taz</title>
      <link>https://betaflight.fr/blog/2018/02/16/bf3-3_1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://betaflight.fr/blog/2018/02/16/bf3-3_1/</guid>
      <description>Betaflight 3.3 Release will be ready for March 1st. New feature : Runaway take off prevention (anti-taz) This feature will prevent uncontrollable acceleration (&amp;lsquo;tasmanian devil&amp;rsquo;) when the craft is armed with misconfigured motor outputs or props on the wrong way, by disarming the craft if such a configuration is detected.
It will also cause disarms when throttling up quickly on the bench with props off.
If you get unwanted disarms right after arming, use the parameters:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Betaflight 3.3 Disarmed while connected</title>
      <link>https://betaflight.fr/blog/2018/02/16/bf3-3_2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://betaflight.fr/blog/2018/02/16/bf3-3_2/</guid>
      <description>Betaflight 3.3 Release will be ready for March 1st. New feature : Arming disabled while connected to Betaflight configurator Arming is now disabled when the flight controller is connected to the Betaflight configurator.
This was added in order to keep users from accidentally arming their craft when testing their RX / mode switches with a battery connected.
In order to enable arming for bench testing, go to the &amp;lsquo;Motors&amp;rsquo; tab and enable the &amp;lsquo;Motor test mode&amp;rsquo; switch (REMOVE ALL PROPELLERS FIRST);</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Betaflight 3.3 FPort</title>
      <link>https://betaflight.fr/blog/2018/02/16/bf3-3_3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://betaflight.fr/blog/2018/02/16/bf3-3_3/</guid>
      <description>Betaflight 3.3 Release will be ready for March 1st. New feature : support for the FrSky FPort protocol FPort is a new RC protocol that was developed by FrSky in collaboration with Betaflight.
It has a number of improvements over existing protocols used by FrSky hardware:
 only one serial connection is required, RC control information, telemetry (including MSP tunneling), and RSSI are all sent over this connection; the serial connection uses 115200, N81, making it easier to implement on hardware that has limited support for &amp;lsquo;exotic&amp;rsquo; modes; it is uninverted (not possible with the test firmware for existing RX).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Downloads</title>
      <link>https://betaflight.fr/downloads/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Feb 2018 21:49:20 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://betaflight.fr/downloads/</guid>
      <description>1. Betaflight Firmwares Binaries firmwares files can be downloaded with the configurator or here
You can compile your own firmware binary, modify and get sources here
2. Betaflight Configurator Binaries of the Configurator can be downloaded here
You can also compile your own configurator, get and modify sources here
3. Betaflight Blackbox Explorer The easiest way to get the explorer (if you have Google Chrome) is to install it from the Chrome Web Store</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://betaflight.fr/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://betaflight.fr/contact/</guid>
      <description>We are here to help you Contact us at our Slack Channel http://www.betaflight.ch/
or
Read our Wiki https://github.com/betaflight/betaflight/wiki
or
Post a Issue / feature request at GitHub https://github.com/betaflight/betaflight/issues</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://betaflight.fr/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://betaflight.fr/faq/</guid>
      <description>Betaflight is a OpenSource Project to get the most of your Quadcopter or Plane. Enjoy FPV and have the latest features available on a whole variation of flightcontrolers.
1. Where to download the latest releases and also see the changelogs? The Downloads entry menu can answer your question. Otherwise You can always find the latest releases on our Github releases Page. There you can also see the latest changelogs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>